- 我告诉过你南瓜的是吗？ - 没
- I told you about the pumpkin, didn't I? - No.
万圣节我给她买了的这个巨大的南瓜。
I bought her this huge pumpkin for Halloween.
她不忍心在上面雕刻所以把南瓜藏起来了。
She couldn't bear to carve it so she saved it.
直到圣诞节。
It ended up under the Christmas tree.
然后格拉默说，在平安夜闻到了令人作呕的气味......
Then Gramoo said on Christmas Eve there was this sickening smell...
......渗透到整个房子里。 - 不是吧
...permeating the entire house. - No.
当我把它捡起来，它的爆炸了，液体在同一时间喷出来。
When I picked it up, it sort of exploded and liquefied at the same time.
这不好笑。 它浸透了格拉默东面的地板。
It wasn't funny. It soaked through Gramoo's Oriental.
现在地板上仍然有一个大的斑点。
There's still a big spot on the floor.
好吧。我们需要些墙纸。 嘿，希斯。
Okay. We need wallpaper paste. Hey, Cece.